isn't this great I can't believe Hatsune
Miku is visiting here all the way from
Japan
hey do you guys think Miku will sign her
name right above my butt cheeks
keep dreaming Manic the only butt cheeks
she's signing today will be mine damn
you guys are just so crazy there's sure
to be enough photographs to go around
especially because we got special
backstage passes
you guys got backstage passes too you
guys must be hard Koehler mickou fans
like us why don't we all go together oh
but only after we get our autographs
first of course this is Joseph my little
bro my name is Mike hello
thank you I just got done beating my
wife's ass I'm glad I could come to the
Miku Expo so I could meet sexy people
such as yourself you know this is the
best day of my life you smell so good
like a ham and cheese sandwich that my
wife makes for me if she doesn't make me
a sandwich
I hit her and tell her to get back in
the kitchen hey hit that Alina movie not
really he didn't drive chingkuo's justo
stand-in Lynnae Goddamnit Uncle Chuck
stop embarrassing us you're totally
uncool
[Music]
miku-miku
in the overview - my son what happened
to my son everyone get out of my [ __ ]
way
Oh No Deal did a domain Goddess
[Music]
nice going everyone that was amazing
hey Miku is going on four o clock you
should wrap this up pretty soon we'll
help you only sign two things you [ __ ]
this is outrageous
it's unfair you had us pay $80 just to
walk in the front door we already paid
you 300 for an autograph - you can't
just leave now now you guys you have to
remember she is just better than you
hey Emma cool maybe they are right don't
you think you should sign a few more
autographs
what is this makuu please forgive me I'm
sorry for disobeying you I won't do it
again
[Music]
okey-dokey boys and girls everything
seems to be in order when you go
backstage take a left and you will find
the meet-and-greet area
[Music]
miss Miku please don't go throwing stuff
on the ground
we're only renting out this bookstore
[Music]
damn that [ __ ] [ __ ] stinks guys look
over there it's the real Hatsune Miku
she's asked beautiful in person as she
is on the computer yet that slide is
[ __ ] sexy
[Music]
no we're the group who bought VIP
tickets to come and meet you
[Music]
now hold the [ __ ] up you [ __ ] we're not
going to let you just walk away the VIP
tickets specifically state that we get
to come backstage and meet you you son
of a [ __ ] those [ __ ] cost us 600
bucks each don't make me shove my fist
up your butt
[Music]
hi guys look over there is that no way
it's the rest of the Vocaloid members
they you're blue like me
aren't you one of the Vocaloids
but check it out gang this blue man with
the big buttt cheeks actually knows who
we are
my name is Catoe
but you probably already know that and
[ __ ]
the twins over here are Rin and Len they
have sex like a lot we try to stop them
but we can't
[Music]
this one over here is the red one I
forgot her name but she's like the Red
Ranger but she's not really the leader
she just wears red the other one is the
pink one I forgot her name too but if
you guys are other Vocaloid members
why weren't you all out front signing
autographs we would have loved to get
you your autograph too Mickey you said
were not allowed to go out front she's
afraid that if we did we would draw all
the attention away from her
that's horrible you guys are Vocaloid
it's just as much has that son of a
[ __ ] you deserve to be out there so you
can sign autographs for all of your fans
here that's right you guys are nobody's
[ __ ] yes stand up for yourselves
maybe so but there's not much we can do
since Miku always has a gun with her
hold on Kaito I think these [ __ ] have
got a point if you ask me I say we go
confront me clue right here right now
she can't run from this while she's
locked in a bathroom stall taking and
[ __ ] this is our one and only chance yet
let's [ __ ] kill that [ __ ]
[Music]
well well well if it isn't the Goddess
herself so Miku how was your pooping of
course Miku
that's what being friends is all about
helping each other we did it bro the
Vocaloids are back together again
[Music]